- Burbank Airport, please.
- Vegas, here we come!
(Bernadette:)No husbands, no boyfriends, no rules.
(Amy:)No rules?
(Amy:)We're not gonna get drunk and have
a six-way with the Blue Man Group, are we?
(Bernadette:)- No.
- So there are some rules.
(Bernadette:)Fine. No husbands, no boyfriends
and some rules.
(Amy:)Thank you. Vegas!
- The ladies are away, the boys will play!
- Anything can happen!
- It's gonna get crazy.
- Dungeons & Dragons!
I got a brand new bikini
so drinks at the pool are on these.
(Bernadette:)I got a sexy new tube top
that says "come hither"...
(Bernadette:)...and a can of pepper spray that says,
"Close enough, Jack."
(Amy:)I got some old underwear I'm gonna throw
onstage at the Garth Brooks concert.
(Penny:)I'm sorry, why old?
Because last time I saw him,
I threw new ones and it got me nothing.
I've got a brand new seven-piece
set of polyhedral dice.